Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
1908-1989
Belluschi, Pietro, 1899-1994.
453.0 linear ft.
Papers of the Italian-American regionalist architect. Collection includes correspondence, plans, blueprints, sketches, tracings, renderings, elevations, mechanical plans, foundation plans, and other papers relating to principally Pacific Northwest buildings or alterations proposed and/or executed by A.E. Doyle and successor firms, including that of Pietro Belluschi.
148840
Biographical History
Pietro Belluschi (1899-1994) was an Italian-American architect and a prominent figure in the Modernist movement. Over the course of his career he was involved in the design of more than a thousand buildings in the United States and abroad.
Born in Ancona, Italy, Belluschi was the son of Guido and Camilla (Dogliani) Belluschi. He studied at the University of Rome's School of Engineering, receiving his doctorate in civil engineering in 1922; he later earned a second degree in engineering from Cornell University in Ithaca, New York. In 1923, he served as the inspector of housing development in Rome in his native country. From 1927 to 1942 he was with A.E. Doyle and Associates (Belluschi became a United States citizen in 1929); and from 1951 to 1965 he was Dean of the School of Architecture and Planning at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
Belluschi won numerous awards for his work, including the American Institute of Architects' Gold Medal in 1972 and a National Medal of Arts for lifetime achievement in 1991. Buildings he designed or was a design consultant for include the Equitable Building in Portland (1948), the Bennington College Library (1957-1958), the Pan Am Building in midtown Manhattan (1963), and the Louise M. Davies Symphony Hall in San Francisco (1980). He was also the principal architect of the Juilliard School of Music, including Alice Tully Hall, at Lincoln Center, New York (1969) and was the design consultant on St. Mary's Cathedral in San Francisco (1971).
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Pietro Belluschi Papers is arranged into twelve series. The bulk of the material is in the first two series, Architectural projects (numbered) and Architectural projects (unnumbered). The next nine series are Job specifications, Correspondence, Shop drawings, Photographs, Financial, Published material, Writings, Architectural projects [General], and Miscellaneous.
Although the Job specifications, Correspondence, Shop drawings, and Photographs are physically arranged in separate series, to make it easier to locate all relevant material, items from these series are listed under the relevant project in Architectural projects (numbered) and Architectural projects (unnumbered).
The final series consists of Correspondence-subject files from a separate accession in 1991.
The first two series, Architectural projects (numbered) and Architectural projects (unnumbered) contain material related to specific numbered and unnumbered architectural projects. These include private homes, churches, dormitories, office buildings, public spaces, performance spaces, and other projects. At the end of the unnumbered projects are a number of miscellaneous items, including maps, non-architectural work (e.g. weathervanes, grates), and unidentified buildings,
Job specifications contains specifications for numbered and unnumbered jobs, as well as unidentified and miscellaneous projects.
Correspondence consists of several subseries, largely in original order: there is a section of correspondence relating to numbered and unnumbered architectural projects, a chronological section (1924-1940), an alphabetical section (A-Z) followed by another alphabetical section (A-Z), A. E. Doyle correspondence (1923-1928), a second chronological section (1912-1927), a third alphabetical section, and a final miscellaneous section. There is overlap between the sections; for example, the two chronological sections overlap by three years, both of the first two alphabetical sections contain material pertaining to the American Institute of Architects, and A. E. Doyle material appears in a number of the sections.
Shop drawings consists largely of drawings pertaining to numbered and unnumbered architectural projects. There is also a small amount (10 folders) of general or unidentified drawings.
Photographs consists of photographs of numbered and unnumbered architectural projects. Photographs have been physically co-located in 13 document boxes and 3 oversize boxes, but are listed in the inventory under the appropriate project.
Financial consists of ledger sheets for alterations to the Commonwealth Building. It is unclear why these were filed separately from other project material.
Published material includes articles, case studies, publicity, and other material pertaining to specific architectural jobs as well as to Belluschi in general.
Writings contains articles and papers written by Belluschi, including several pieces on church architecture.
Architectural projects [General] contains material on a range of numbered and unnumbered architectural projects, as well as general categories of work such as "Early west coast work" and "Miscellaneous consulting."
Miscellaneous appears to be mostly memorabilia. It includes awards, some pamphlets relating to Lincoln Center, magazine clippings, etc.
Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession consists of a second set of files donated later, in original order. Most relates to Belluschi's work in the 1970s and 1980s, including the Kerr-McGee Center in Oklahoma, the Seattle Convention Center, the St. Louis Synagogue, work with Jun & Brannen, and Bellushi's work with various committees and juries.
Arrangement of the Collection
Numbered and unnumbered jobs are stored in the Tube Wall. Refer to the inventory below for specific locations. Renderings and hard back sketches are arranged alphabetically by job type (e.g. Banks, Schools) and within that alphabetically by job name. The last category, Miscellaneous, includes jobs which do not fit into a particular category. Photographs in Drawers are arranged in the same way.
Note that the inventory lists Drawers SD 1 through SD 8. This is incorrect. There are only FIVE SD drawers. Some effort may be needed to locate material in these drawers.
Related Material
has the papers of numerous notable modern architects. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Architects; Belluschi, Pietro, 1899-1994.; Doyle, A. E.; Architects -- United States.; Architectural design.; Architectural drawing -- United States -- 20th century.; Architectural firms.; Architectural practice.; Architecture -- United States.; Architecture -- Designs and plans.; Architecture -- Details.; Architecture, American.; Architecture -- Northwestern States.; Architecture, Domestic -- United States.; Architecture -- United States -- 20th century.; Church architecture -- United States.; Italian Americans.; Regionalism in architecture.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Blueprints (reprographic copies); Correspondence.; Photographs.; Specifications.; Architects.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Unprocessed portions of the collection are not available for research.
Acquisition Information
Bulk of collection, gift of Pietro Belluschi or his estate, 1964-1999.
Charles Sprague Lodge drawings, gift of Martha Sprague Hurley, 2010.
Inventory
- Architectural projects, numbered
  Material in this series is listed numerically by job number. The job title is given, if know. If not, the job title is given as "[Unknown]". Note that since Belluschi had many repeat clients, a given job (e.g. the Equitable Building) may be found under several different job numbers. In addition, in some cases material related to a specific building or client did not have a job number written on it, so additional material may also be found in the next series, " Architectural projects, unnumbered," under the name of the client or building.
  - 1 J. F. Bell Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 256)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 2 Security Loan and Investment Company [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 256)
  - 3 C. W. Collins
    - Shop drawings (Box 256)
    - Shop drawings (Box 257)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 4 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 6 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 7 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 9 Presbyterian Church [Religious]
    - Shop drawings (Box 257)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 10 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 12 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 15 Worcester Building [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 257)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 16 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 18 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 19 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 20 H. S. Nichols
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
    - Shop drawings (Box 257)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 21 W. L. Brewster [Residential]
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 22 K. G. Lundstrum
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 25 F. H. Kage
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 26 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 29 Eastside Branch Library, Portland OR [Library]
    - Photographs, includes magazine clipping, floor plan (Box 431)
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 31 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 32 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 33 Hartman and Thompson
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 35 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
  - 36 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 1)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 37 Shogren [Residential]
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 2)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 38 Harmon
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Specifications (Box 2)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 39 W. L. Brewster [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:6)
    - Shop drawings, "original restricted; please use disc in folder" (Box 259)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
  - 40 Meier and Frank Multipurpose Building [Commercial]
    - Photographs, includes floor plan; could also be Job 1199; 2 folders (Box 431)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 259)
    - Shop drawings (Box 260)
    - Specifications, 5 folders (Box 2)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 230)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 41 Honeyman [Commercial]
    - Shop drawings (Box 260)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 42 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 3)
  - 43 Rummelin, McClelland
    - Shop drawings (Box 260)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 44 C. E. Curry Residence [Residential]
    - Shop drawings (Box 260)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 47 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 3)
  - 48 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 49 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 3)
  - 50 Louis Burke
    - Shop drawings (Box 260)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 51 H. L. Parker [or L. H. Parker]
    - Drawings, house (Drawer SD 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 261)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 53 Don / Dan Malarkey [Residential]
    - Shop drawings (Box 261)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 55 [unknown]
    - Specifications, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 59 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 60 Rummelin
    - Shop drawings (Box 261)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 61 [William?] Hanley
    - Drawings, country house (Drawer SD 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 261)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 64 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 3)
  - 65 Corbett
    - Shop drawings (Box 261)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 66 First Presbyterian Church, Portland, OR [Religious], 1910
    - Drawings, 87 items (Tube 311)
    - Shop drawings (Box 261)
    - Shop drawings (Box 262)
    - Specifications (Box 3)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 67 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 3)
  - 68 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
  - 72 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
  - 73 St. Vincent's Hospital, Doyle & Patterson [Hospital], 1908
    - Drawings (Tube 312)
    - Drawings (Tube 313)
  - 74 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 75 First National Bank, Coquille [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 262)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 231)
  - 76 St. Vincent's Hospital [Hospital]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 262)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 77 [S. M.?] Mears Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
    - Specifications (Box 262)
  - 78 H. E. Noble Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 262)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 79 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 80 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
  - 81 W. C. Alvord
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 3)
    - Shop drawings (Box 263)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 82 Sisters of Holy Name [Religious]
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Drawings, provincial house (Drawer MCD 8)
    - Shop drawings (Box 263)
    - Shop drawings (Box 264)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 83 Corbett-O'Shea (Lipmann-Wolf)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 6 folders (Box 5)
    - Shop drawings (Box 264)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
    - Specifications (Box 265)
  - 84 Neighborhood House [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 87 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
  - 90 Olds, Wortman and King [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 265)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 91 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 92 Selling Building [Commercial]
    - Drawings [Commercial], 1911 (Tube 314)
    - Drawings [Commercial], 1911 (Tube 315)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 265)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 232)
  - 93 S. Frank
    - Shop drawings (Box 265)
  - 94 [unknown]
    - Shop drawings (Box 265)
  - 95 Corbett-O'Shea (Lipmann-Wolf)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Shop drawings (Box 265)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 99 C. K. Williams
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 3)
    - Shop drawings (Box 266)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 102 W. L. Brewster Alterations [Residential]
    - Shop drawings (Box 266)
  - 104 Fred Strong
    - Shop drawings (Box 266)
  - 105 Mae and Anne Shogren / Shongren / Shogrin Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 258)
    - Shop drawings (Box 266)
  - 106 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
  - 109 [unknown]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD)
  - 110 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
  - 112 Olds, Wortman and King [Commercial]
    - Shop drawings (Box 266)
  - 115 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
  - 122 Robert H. Strong Building, Doyle & Patterson [Commercial], 1910
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Tube 316)
    - Shop drawings (Box 267)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 123 Mrs. H. W. Nunn [Residential]
    - Shop drawings (Box 267)
  - 124 Eastside Branch Library, Portland, OR [Library], 1911
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Tube 317)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 267)
    - Shop drawings (Box 268)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 125 E. R. Corbett
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 268)
  - 126 [unknown; possibly Reed College Hall of Arts & Sciences]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 10)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 127 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 128 Mrs. J. C. Rummelin Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 268)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 129 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
  - 132 Reed College [Educational]
    - Shop drawings (Box 269)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 133 Atiyeh Brothers [Commercial]
    - Shop drawings (Box 269)
  - 134 J. C. Baird
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
    - Shop drawings (Box 269)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 135 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
  - 136 C. E. Wolverton, Judge [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Shop drawings (Box 269)
  - 140 J. G. Beach
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 7)
    - Shop drawings (Box 270)
  - 141 Woodward, Clarke & Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Shop drawings (Box 270)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 233)
  - 142 Old Oregon Hotel (Benson) [Residential]
    - Correspondence, 9 folders (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Drawings [Residential], 1911 (Tube 318)
    - Drawings [Residential], 1911 (Tube 319)
    - Drawings [Residential] (Tube 320)
    - Drawings, miscellaneous work (Tube 460)
    - Photographs, includes magazine clippings; 2 folders (Box 431)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 271)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 272)
    - Sketches [Residential] (Tube 321)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 143 Stephen Mead Estate
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
    - Shop drawings (Box 273)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 145 Woodward, Clarke & Co., Woodlark Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Shop drawings (Box 273)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 148 Reed College, North Dormitory [Educational]
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Shop drawings (Box 273)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 274)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 149 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 150 Multnomah Library [Library]
    - Shop drawings (Box 274)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 275)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 276)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 277)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 151 Oregon St. Normal School, Monmouth, OR [Educational], 1912
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Tube 535)
    - Shop drawings (Box 278)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 152 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
  - 153 Shasta Hotel [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Shop drawings (Box 278)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 154 Portland Trust Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
    - Shop drawings (Box 278)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 155 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 157 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
  - 158 [unknown; possibly Reed College power house]
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 159 Ford Motor Co. Service Plant, Portland OR [Commercial], 1912
    - Correspondence, 6 folders (Box 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Tube 324)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:1)
    - Shop drawings (Box 278)
    - Shop drawings (Box 279)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 234)
  - 160 Voorhies, Gordon
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Shop drawings (Box 279)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 161 Seeley, Mrs. A. C. [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Shop drawings (Box 279)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 164 Oregon Electric Railway Depot [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 280)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 165 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 166 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 167 Morgan & Bushong Investment Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 280)
    - Shop drawings (Box 281)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 170 Multnoman County Library [Library]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 281)
    - Shop drawings (Box 282)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 171 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
  - 172 Alterations to Oregon Hotel [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Drawings [Residential], 1909 (Tube 325)
    - Shop drawings (Box 282)
  - 173 Oregon Normal School Boiler House
    - Shop drawings (Box 282)
  - 175 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
  - 176 Northwest Fidelity Bank [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 10 folders (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 11 folders (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 282)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 283)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 284)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 285)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 286)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 287)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 288)
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 177 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 16)
  - 178 [unknown; possibly Reed College women's building]
    - Correspondence (Box 16)
  - 179 [unknown]
    - Specifications, Doyle and Patterson pamphlets (Box 235)
  - 185 Pittock Block [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 16)